happysale.in 2016-05-02

# Privacy Policy - Happy Sale

The privacy of our users is important to us. Hence, below are the ways we will use and safeguard your personal information that we receive and collect when you use and visit our site happysale.in. If you have any doubts regarding this policy, or on how we use and process your personal information, please contact us by sending us an e-mail at [privacy@happysale.in](mailto:privacy@happysale.in).

BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT PROCEED FURTHER TO USE THIS WEBSITE.

### Log Files

We collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include user’s IP (internet protocol) address, user’s ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser user used to visit our site (such as Firefox or Internet Explorer), exact time user visited our site, and pages user visited in our site.

### Email Address

Happy Sale is a free content web site. We do not require any information from users (not even a user name or password). We do not sell any information from our site to any outside party. The only e-mail sent from our websites is in response to an inquiry that any user may send us or as a result of subscribing to our double opt-in e-mail list.

### Privacy Policy of Third Parties

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information by Happy Sale through your interaction with the web sites. Other web sites/merchants that are accessible through links from our site may have their own privacy policies and personal information collection, use, and disclosure practices. Our merchants and business partners may have their own privacy statements as well. We want users to verify the privacy statements provided by these third parties prior to providing them with any information or taking advantage of an offer or promotion.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as personal preferences when user visits our site. This could include showing user only a pop-up at the first visit, or access to some of our features, such as forums. We allow advertisers and other third parties as well to place cookies onto your computer when you visit their website.

The cookies placed by advertisers and other third parties are used to keep track of the web searches you make while visiting their website, as well as your web surfing behavior on this website and other websites you may visit. This information is used to show you advertisements tailored to your interests on this and other websites, and/or to keep track of your response to each ad.

Users can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in their browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how users are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to log in to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
